puts "CREATING YOUR FRIGGING FLASHCARDS!!!"

Flashcard.create(question: "The only planet that has a day longer than its year is ...", answer: "venus", subject: "Science" option_one: "venus", option_two: "mars", option_three: "jupiter", user_id: 1);
Flashcard.create(question: "The naturalist responsible for the theory of evolution by natural selection is which one of the following?", answer: "Charles Darwin", subject: "Science" option_one: "Albert Einstein", option_two: "Johannes Kepler", option_three: "Charles Darwin" user_id: 1);
Flashcard.create(question: "The North Star is which one of the following?", answer: "Polaris", subject: "Science" option_one: "Polaris", option_two: "Alpha Centari", option_three: "Orion" user_id: 1);
Flashcard.create(question: "Who was the first American to orbit the earth?", answer: "John Glenn", subject: "Science" option_one: "Jim Lovell", option_two: "John Glenn", option_three: "Buzz Aldrin" user_id: 1);
Flashcard.create(question: "All land-dwelling living things need which of the following as the initial source of energy for fuel?", answer: "sunlight", subject: "Science" option_one: "sunlight", option_two: "water", option_three: "chlorophyll" user_id: 1);
Flashcard.create(question: "Which one of the following is a nocturnal animal?", answer: "bat", subject: "Science" option_one: "bear", option_two: "deer", option_three: "bat" user_id: 1);
Flashcard.create(question: "A honey bee getting nectar or pollen from a flower is an example of which type of association?", answer: "mutualism", subject: "Science" option_one: "mutualism", option_two: "commensalism", option_three: "parasitism" user_id: 1);
Flashcard.create(question: "The standard unit of measurement used for measuring force is which of the following?", answer: "newton", subject: "Science" option_one: "kilogram", option_two: "watt", option_three: "newton" user_id: 1);
Flashcard.create(question: "Which of the following is the hottest planet?", answer: "venus", subject: "Science" option_one: "uranus", option_two: "venus", option_three: "mercury" user_id: 1);
Flashcard.create(question: "What is the name of the igneous rock that is light enough to float?", answer: "pumice", subject: "Science" option_one: "granite", option_two: "basalt", option_three: "pumice" user_id: 1);

























puts "FLASHCARDS FRIGGING CREATED!!!"